const questions = [
    { questionText: 'A Waterfall model is ___ for software engineering', answerOptions: ['Good', 'Not the best'], correctAnswer: 'Not the best'},
    { questionText: 'A measure of stability is___', answerOptions: ['Change Failure Rate', 'Frequency'], correctAnswer: 'Change Failure Rate'},
    { questionText: 'React is a Java framework', answerOptions: ['True', 'False'], correctAnswer: 'False'},
    { questionText: 'Which of the following is an aspect of Agile Development?', answerOptions: ['Scrums', 'Refractor'], correctAnswer: 'Scrums'},
    { questionText: 'What is the first step of TDD (Test-Driven Development)', answerOptions: ['Green', 'Red'], correctAnswer: 'Red'},
    { questionText: 'How many object instances does a singleton pattern handle?', answerOptions: ['One', 'Three'], correctAnswer: 'One'},
    { questionText: 'Which of the following does Hungarian Notation organize?', answerOptions: ['Variable Names', 'Integers'], correctAnswer: 'Variable Names'},
    { questionText: 'The unitended expansion of your original plan would be called a ____', answerOptions: ['Feature Creep', 'Scope Creep'], correctAnswer: 'Scope Creep'},
    { questionText: 'Microservices are monolithic', answerOptions: ['True', 'False'], correctAnswer: 'False'},
    { questionText: 'Which of the following is a benefit of using the Cloud?', answerOptions: ['Tight coupling', 'Start-up time'], correctAnswer: 'Start-up time'},
    
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  